lambopower.com 2006-03-31

# LamboForums.com Site Information

| Information Menu  
---  
› Forum Rules  
› **Privacy Policy**  
› Site Icons  
› List of Advertisers  
› Advertising Info  
› Official Banners  
|  |  **» LamboForums.com Privacy Policy**  
---  
Information Collection and Use  
LamboForums.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways that differ from what is disclosed in this statement.  
Links  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [LamboForums.com] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.   
Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, track user's movement, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.   
Security  
LamboForums.com takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit information via the web site this information is protected both online and off-line.  
Confidentiality of Personal Information  
We will not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to others outside of LamboForums.com. Any information that you provide will not be attributable to you, as collected information is generally viewed at the aggregate level.   
Legal Disclaimer  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or to comply with a legal process served on our web site.   
Cookies  
Our site may use cookies to help track usage patterns on our site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this, is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on their sites. However, we have no access to, or control over these cookies.   
Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
Contact Us  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please [Contact Us](http://www.lamboforums.com/forum/sendmessage.php)  
**Posted on November 27, 2005**
